If the body of a joy base
truly existed,
then it could never be reborn
as something else, a different kind of model.
And the five objects of the
senses, these seem
attached to the celestial form as if
they truly existed, could
never appear as if
they existed in any other way.
In that case,
could anyone ever attach themselves
to the four other objects of the senses—sounds
and everything else? If
they did, then it would be a
contradiction
for the colors and shapes they've already
focused on, this assurance
that they truly existed.
And their "that is real" would be... I'm sorry,
but
what it means is... it would be very profound. I'm
already sorry that we didn't get as
far yesterday,
not at the pace of 100 years.
I think people were really happy about
yesterday, and also about the
questions and answers. I would say let's,
and we will have questions and answers.
So they're still talking about
someone who was a very good person
in this life. I'll try
to speak slowly for the translator.
I always get a little excited at...
Tomorrow,
and that's why something very rich
and influential was offered again,
and even after being reborn,
they see things wrong. That's one of the
reasons why they had to be reborn.
We did good things, but they
really didn't understand what they were doing.
They thought that
the people they did good things for
existed out there and couldn't
be their own. In this case,
it's very interesting.
It's the opposite of the
husband in the kitchen problem.
So, if you go into the kitchen and people are shouting at each other,
then you feel attacked
because you don't understand that we're coming from you.
You don't understand that, so
you feel attacked because of it.
Here, the opposite is the underlying
problem. These people here did good
things for other people
in this life,
but they didn't really understand
what the data meant. And they
thought that people would come to them of their own accord.
Now we come
to a good question, a very interesting
question. It's
possible to do the
wrong things even though you're
doing the right things.
So, in this case, this...  Was the
person very generous to other people?
Perhaps they
shared a lot of money or other things, but
they had the same problems as
the woman in the kitchen. They thought
the other people they gave money to
came from outside, from that direction. In
the ancient books, I'll give you a
new word now.
I think I can do this here. It's
their new motto.
To do means
that the pen
comes to them. This means they see
the pen as if it will provide security.
Basically, they are
everything as if a
sixth exists, themselves,
and they understand me.
Only a husband comes from them,
and also the other people to whom
they net. If the people they
love, perhaps even people in the
kitchen to whom they give money,
then good deeds are over. But they
are good deeds,
dirty good deeds. This means you don't
understand
that the money you give to other people does
n't come from that direction, that the
other people you give the money to do
n't come from that direction either.
So even if you do good things,
you make a mistake in  Your mind, you
believe the money you give people
comes from the other side, comes from
the factory, the money was
printed, and you believe that I give
something to the person somewhere, that results in them coming
from this direction,
maybe that's your mother
or father, you understand me, that
they also come from you,
what happens to these people,
they get a good rebirth,
but the seeds run out because they do
n't understand that
I be
[Music],
these have created this new body,
have
this superhero body in the DEFA,
in the countries of the DMSB, what does that mean,
the superhero body that one
can get if one is very nice,
special people in some tradition,
when they talk about heaven,
maybe they have seen something like that,
it's not always real because one ca
n't stay there,
and the camera runs out, the seeds run out,
you were generous, but at the same time you
misunderstood the
person to whom the generous was, so
again, you don't understand that we get
things from
you and talk more, she was
something very interesting now, if this  The
[music]
he was reborn there
if he doesn't come
if it if she doesn't come then then
she is somewhat sad
because she can't enjoy everything in the
temporary heaven of the de.
Of course, she enjoys it. What do you mean
by that? Clearly, they have great food.
They probably have donuts
everywhere, and
they are very strong and beautiful, and they
are so beautiful actually
that their heaven of form is
called the realm of form. What is
meant by that is the realm of beauty. So why is there
a problem
described? What do you mean by that? So it's like this:
they can only see things.
They can't hear anything.
They can't smell.
They can't taste.
If that's it, then it's not
for me because they can't
have donuts. You just see
beautiful things, and you can't eat anything,
and
they can't feel anything either. If they touch
anything else, if
they touch another teacher,
and then the devilish part of
your mind comes into play. Special pages set up.
But that's not true. I heard
that these devers
can throw the planets around.  can
play baseball or football with planets
and of course if they
join
[Music]
they go to the beer garden after the
game
[Music]
I saw that in Munich in
Munich
that's just not true of course
they can see things they can have
conversations they can kick planets
no they can't
[Music]
why not the Panchen Lama says no
they can't why not because
if they saw them
then they think that these things
are self-existent and from the outside the
things they see come from
his point of view
they also come from the outside
the colors and the shapes
they see come from the outside that is very
difficult that is very very difficult
if color and shape come from the outside
they do not change if color and
shape come from the outside
you can't between to a beautiful
song and then you also can't the side on just
body of a god for the sake of it
because because they do not
change the colors and shapes colors
and already if they come from the outside then
they do not change and then of
course you think of course if
they come from his point of view too  The sun goes down, the
moon comes out of
fashion, and even in those areas
things change in
nature, in
nature things change
and the planets move, that does
n't depend on us,
and then the first run I was
thinking about it again,
nature, we like those who want it, you should, you should,
and you should get away from the
screen, out into nature,
always some fresh air, and look at
the stones and the trees.
Two weeks ago she even went with me, she even went fighting
alone
without me because she also said that
I would come along,
and we call it nature, right
English nature,
and nature means humans did
n't do it, we didn't create it
because a woman loves to go into the woods
or the mountains
and she doesn't like it, I wanted to
take her to Paris once but she didn't want to,
we see each other
and mountains, that's nature, but nature, if
you think about it,
nature doesn't mean to acquire, the
word nature means
she doesn't want to go to the Louvre in Paris
because someone wanted to create it, and
it's full of things that humans
created, like the  Mona Lisa
wants to see something natural that was
n't created by humans, but according to
us,
it's not like 50 percent of the world was
made by humans. It's not like
humans created the cities we
have and nature
created itself. That's not how it is.
Humans made everything, the
living beings, animals and humans. We've
always had everything. We also have the
oceans, the trees,
and the mountains. There is
no nature
that nature takes; that's a lie.
Nature primarily means
societies, of course,
but
actually, we made everything.
Okay, understand that there is
no movement in the universe that does
n't come from your mind. The stars don't move,
but they don't go down from the outside. The
mouth doesn't open and go down.
This planet doesn't rotate on its
own axis from its own sides.
So what comes from us? Everything comes from
us.
If everything we see
came from the outside, if
the blue sky, for example, didn't
come from me, but
the blue sky in the world came from the blue sky,
then I could never hear anything.
That remains the first fan, long since
here.  If the blue sky
I see with my eyes were
natural,
and I hadn't created it,
and it simply came towards me,
if the blue sky were natural,
then you could never hear anything
because it wouldn't come from the outside,
it would come from Dirk, from
nature.
Then the sound would also come from nature,
and it wouldn't come from outside.
If sounds come from nature, from within themselves,
then you couldn't switch and look
at something beautiful like the sky,
switch to something higher because of a good
rock 'n' roll song, like the one you're reading.
I don't know if this is legal, sorry,
I
heard it this morning. It's a
beautiful song about dying, too.
Whatever people always say here,
if the world were natural,
if the blue sky were natural
and could come from the blue sky,
then you could never hear water
because it wouldn't change. There would be
no reason to change it.
Nature would simply do its own thing;
it wouldn't change. It
's very interesting who he's talking about.
He's still talking about this guy who
was very generous in his life
but had dirty good karma,
rulers,
and
a lot of super bodies.
Superhero body, but he can't
say why not, because he can't change anymore, why not,
because
he didn't come to statements, he was just
reborn, he came from nature, he
comes from nature,
this way here,
you have to understand, you have to understand that
we're talking about nature here, okay Marianne,
one question, are you ready, Greek,
percent of the world comes from us, how
much percent of the world comes from, comes
from the world,
everything comes from us, yes, exactly 100 percent,
yes, we have a joke, we have a
joke, DC100,
100.0 percent
comes from us,
if one percent didn't come from us,
then maybe you could think of a,
maybe you could
listen to a song after being in a suitcase,
if it came from the outside,
if it came from the outside, of course,
then you couldn't change from the
symbol on the red rose
because there's no reason for it to
change,
nature has no, no forces, there are
none there, there is no light, there is
no attraction, is
electricity, there is
no magnetism,
everything comes from us,
okay, here's Peter  Timm, do you
still have a sacrifice for me? Thank you, Marianne. You, you
are, you have completed it. So there must be
a good background to the...
I like your hairstyle,
by the way.
Okay, the next victim, world,
Markus Zahl.
And if you are now in Germany or
in any other language,
and if the beings of joy
look at their daughters with this version of
love, which they consider so lovely, and
the love they see in a way that would depend on nothing, would depend on nothing,
as something true, in a way
that could never change,
it could never change to
look different, and that would be a direct
contradiction to the fact that if
these beings of joy fight with their
cousins, their feelings might
change,
if these friends, beings of joy, could start
to lead, then
that would be a contradiction
of the idea that their lovely love
existed as reality and
was dependent on nothing else. Yes, very nice.
By the way, this whole face of theirs...
it's a special kind of philosophy in
the ancient books, it's
called... I'll give you 100 dollars.  What does "
aktien" mean? We had it recently.
You asked me something about it. The
spelling after "zu" means "good day." X
means
unchanging. That's another day. Was
I? This "dankbar" is
written differently. "Is" means grateful. "Tasten"
means, in theory,
founder written
in the stars. No, that's not it. It's war.
Here lies. It
means
if what you say was it. If what
you say is true, then there is
this problem. This problem. This problem
and the problem. That's why
this whole part of it. In
English,
we have to say "would be"
or "could" because
it's okay because the verb "selbst" (self/subject).
If it was what you say,
then there would be no love. Then there would be no
hate.
Then there would be no wars. If that
was what you say,
this is a special kind of logic, and
it makes English very hard to
read. It's open-ended, but don't give me...
I didn't write the Tibetan. So he
says there is
a kind of love that is
here and in Japan, and in the
Tibetan language here, it means
this kind of love that
when you look at something, it
looks very, very beautiful. It's a
special kind of love. I love the  1000
citizens if someone can tell me where
this kind of love is mentioned 1000
dollars
it is in the points
cause and effect
how to develop politics
it is one of the steps to develop politicians to
lead this kind of love
only it has
I am so proud of my team
he is believe he started
walking yesterday I don't know if it was the first time
it was the first time before I saw
against
and of course I got videos of it
and the other kids like
here I look that he quoted he just
started walking
we are so excited it means we do
n't have to carry 30 kilos with us anymore
but how the mother has her child
why she hits me three videos every hour
because she has this intense love
and it is called here and Janker it
is the love that the child sees as the forehead
when this idea what
her own daughters in heaven look at who were
born there in her shots
then they feel this love that just for
my knee they are the child as very
very beautiful
according to her is
some percent of it of  the love and
a love of these daughters
from nature comes this way
some percent
daughter also exists this way and
I love the tour will the daughter
also comes this one in this picture and I
meet the daughter with my love
runs towards me on this from this
direction and I feel love but for
my knowledge how I mine and he says
if that were true
if that is so if that is what
really happens and the people we
love 50 percent on this from this
direction comes then okay then
Saturday is a nice place for the demo
they have no problems according to them
they have no problems at all what are
the problems of the device do you remember
they have a problem
or 23
they always fight with their with the demi with with
the almost done there is always
a contest between here and secondly
their seeds leak because they
were generous but didn't know how so
and thirdly they have very terrible
pictures very independent now would if
their seeds leak according to them corresponds to the devil
yes exactly
here on the side
and here is I think I don't know in
my head in between  They are arguing with
each other, a carpenter tries
to think
and he wants to, says no, no, these
daughters are, they love my tree, comes
from my side,
and then the angel said no, no, no, they are not coming,
supposedly his jersey
could,
said the devil is coming,
then he says no, if my
life really came from the drive, then
we would never have anyone, then
I wouldn't hate vegetables,
okay, she finally gave up, will experience
vegetables,
first she tried, put them
in the fridge and tried, and
when I didn't eat them,
and then one comes around,
we have a big blender,
okay, I told her, you, when you
make vegetables, I don't like them, but I put them
in the change, and I already a
little, just not to it, and make
possible, not out, and then she said
that's disgusting, I worked so hard
to cook and prepare them,
and
if it were true that the vegetables would
come from the vegetable side, then
I would never have done it,
if it's true that
Miley comes from my tree,
then I would never have anyone,
then it would never change because
it doesn't come from me, it comes from him,
but we know
that these  Heavenly beings, these things were
very big, terrible wars
with them, which means that in
their ideas, cuisine, cousins, their
cousins ​​are not so beautiful and
are very jealous. In
other words, if part of the world
were natural,
then your feelings
of love could never change so much because we...
because the objects, the children you
see and the enemies you see,
they would come from their own side all the time.
They would
never change, so your feelings
towards them could not
change either. So now we have two
changes.
If your son, My Tree,
comes from the same side, then you should never
hear what he says. You can see them,
but you could never become what he
says, or smell, or taste, or
touch
because that would be a change
in nature, and according to you, nature is
locked up, and your love
will be the same all the time. If you were to
love in the morning because you are
upset with My Tree,
then you wouldn't have to
hear anything else all day
because the things outside would
never change. Why not? Because there is
no reason for nature to change.  They
change
nature through their own thing.
It doesn't have to change. The sky doesn't change,
the mountains don't change.
Okay,
two-thirds of
Markus plays music. I don't know because
[music]
microphone.
And yet, when these beings look at their
cousins, customers, the legs, joy beings,
and at first, very intense feelings of
hate to beauty. This hate itself looks like there might be a
possibility.
When the wars then come to an end
and the joy beings
return to their own lands,
and the time goes back
to look at their heavenly daughters with the
feelings of love and see them again as
lovely, that would then be a
contradiction or idea that their hate had felt in
them before. A possibility
exists in, and if this perception of
their daughters as lovely could arise again as
new and fresh in their hearts,
then that would contradict the
lovely live in reality.  It would have existed,
very nicely, then that it's
very, very difficult again in English, and
in Tibetan it's very, very
difficult because all of this,
everything, if it's all written in this
band form, if
what you say is true, then this would
happen here, it's very difficult to translate,
it's very difficult to read, you have to
think about it,
that's
a point here,
so obviously if we
hurt someone by not liking them, I don't know, I had people
here in the
diamond business
and I liked them, and we had a
big building, I think 13 floors at the
moment, and I remember
[music]
when I came to work in the morning, I
thought I wouldn't run into them.
I think you know that
from your company too, you've also been out and about in business,
you
come into the building and you make a
little prayer, have a gate, I hope they
're not in the elevator, if I ever,
office work, there are people like that
you don't want to see, and
not liking these people, do
you think that
comes from their own side,
the reason why you don't want it in the elevator,
you don't think that's from
you.  They come, she thinks, from the
subway. Unfortunately, her point came too rarely,
her train to set, to go together into the
building and go together, even if to,
and it feels to me as if
they come from their own time.
That's the reason why she doesn't like it
and you don't like it, and that does
n't change, and this goes even deeper, this way
goes even deeper.
We can talk about this way for a
week,
but there's also this feeling in
your heart that the juice comes from its
own side.
That's what the first line here is about. The picture is about
the people who also came to them, whom
I don't like.
It looks as if it comes from her
side, and it looks as if
all the things she
always says to me come from
her own side. And
then, and then I start not to like her,
and
I start to pray that I don't run into her too, and
then you believe the attachment you have to the hate, the hate for those who do
n't like it,
and you believe that this also comes from the outside.
Somehow this comes  You also have it
from the outside and he can't
change
if the person
[music]
you wouldn't even
come from their own side at work and
you would meet them in the morning,
then you should have it all day long, even
if you
go home and your daughter or son looks at you like that,
or as if either
because these feelings can't come
together from theirs or yours. So now there
's also Thiele,
the person you don't like, yes, the
former one, really disgusting,
where does he come from? Well, now
probably two for three days, 30,000 times already,
I think the
husband could from his own side,
and where does the annoyed spirit come from?
Where does he come from?
I don't know, I think if
my husband is stupid, then I'm
irritated, do you understand, understand that
she irritated me, also from your perspective. The
husband you see comes from you
and
your reaction to it also comes from
the sayings, and that's why
it's very hard to
escape his counterpart. There would be a natural one,
because natural reactions are
n't natural.  come up and lonely,
probably there are people in the
universe,
if you call them by their names, they love each other
despite life, who despite life,
we have said that if someone is allowed to call us,
we also have other things that
irritate us because of this, and that doesn't have to be the case.
It is also possible that
someone hurts you and you feel
happy as if you were to see me, the one who
runs across the park. It is
also possible if it comes from you, if
it were to come from the outside,
then when you come home and look at your
own child again,
then you should
feel exactly the same way you are led towards the
other person. Here,
for example, there is the case that
they give me war
with the others, there was a smaller one
who are envious of them and always
want to wage war against them. According to them,
if these opponents come from the outside,
the opponent in my country does not come from me,
then I should feel good about it when I
think about them, and I should feel good
when I come home
and see my family, then I would
lead it myself because it does not come from me.
Why shouldn't it
change now? It comes from the outside, it is
natural,
it is  Of course, allow your opponents,
then he has another
comment here. It
says
he has, if you felt when they drew war on you
[music],
and when they come back home,
or the hatred alongside the desire to work
against someone in your office, if that
person were to come of their own accord and
not from you,
then you should take the hatred home with you.
This hatred should never
change if it doesn't come from you.
And even
if you could lose the hatred,
even if you could stop the hatred, there's
no logical reason why
love could arise if you think it's right. There's
no reason why love would
begin when you come home.
So, two kinds of changes
that never happen: your hatred
would never change, and even
if it did
change, you could never begin
with new love when
you come home because everything
comes from the outside. Everything is natural;
it doesn't come from you. And
what's the point? You can only
hate people if it comes from you,
and you can only love people if it does
n't come from you.
And if it does come from you, then there is
no  Reason to hate them or to lie,
you have to create here,
it's very interesting,
it's very, very subtle. Do
you have another German victim for
me? We're going to
move to Washington now. Rocking, the high
performers, the nerves. I'm
sorry for all the squalor.
I thought Cobit this week, but I
've already... Haye, my
wife told me.
My wife told me, you may blow
your nose, but you may not look inside it.
Just this
with a method to implement
the concept in reality
could exist. It's the same for everything else in the
universe; it simply hasn't existed.
If it could exist in the only state of our
minds that exists of itself,
then you can't ever
begin or start
or stop or go anywhere in the universe,
or the laws of karma
themselves exist in name.
I know how, but this translation is
really good,
so just talk to me about the
opponents of DEFA and do
n't just talk about the
family members. Look, do
n't just come into your life in the
morning, into your life from his
side, and the people you have in your  If you do
n't like the office, they don't come from
their own side, and again, quite incidentally,
forget the people you love and do you like the people
you don't give up?
Nothing else in the world comes from
their own side. Okay, we've
now had the people we don't like,
your
opponents, and the people you mix, for
example, the daughters. The topic is, they don't
come from their own side, but wait a
minute, if the things you love do
n't come from their own side, and
the people like you don't
come from their own side either, then
nothing else in the world comes from
their own side, from nothing,
and then inside, even
your own mind doesn't come from its
own world, and that's very important.
It's not just that
the people you love, like my
trick for example, come from you. It's also not
just that the people you don't even love,
or who are neutral towards you,
come from you. Even
a reaction to these people,
love and hate,
all comes from the things
that he composes from this world and
nature,
and there in  Natural reactions
towards them, hating the people you do
n't like and daring to love people,
come from you and
you don't have to live it.
It comes from slowly, very slowly,
changing.
If someone has hurt you or
hurt your country, it's really possible that you
could love them even more.
Why? Because the feelings you
feel towards them also come from you.
They also come from the...
I grew up in Christianity and
there's a prayer book.
It's so beautiful. It has
influenced me a lot my whole life. It's the most
beautiful thing I've ever
read.
And some people say it was from checks. They were
visited
and they studied and led here.
This is the Church of England and they studied it.
No, it was
n't written by Shakespeare.
It was someone else. I don't have a
name. Don't forget... because
someone from that time
had a very interesting life.
Why?
Because
Jesus said
love your enemies like you, a
small family, and yourself.
You should... Now ask
the saints with the same...  Love how you
and your family live, and this
bishop who wrote the prayer book,
he lived it completely and he
tried to do it,
and there was a seat in England. If you
have no money,
then completely hurt, this bishop
tries to become your enemy
because he believes in it so much, nurture this
philosophy, he will give data, money every week. He
believes so strongly that you should
treat your enemies as well as your family
that if you are lucky,
you will seem to become completely
dishonest and I will be made to feel that way your whole
life. It's so cool that
the natural reaction towards
your enemies,
the natural reaction
towards people who are different from the
numbers, is also not natural, it is
changeable, it comes from loneliness and
that the holder, old old people say because it depends on
you misunderstanding your
opponent. The reaction
of a child towards them depends on having to
understand
what
then it goes for countless lives. When you
finally understand
that your opponent comes from you,
then it is possible that you
can truly lie to them, then you could
truly love them,
only maybe  Because they are the opponent
there,
and
if your feelings could change it,
then the whole universe could
n't change, and then there would be no change. That's how
the bachelor ends
this part. I am an opponent, then I ca
n't be honest. And if your feelings
towards him don't make you dizzy,
then don't say anything, then
forget to practice. So I
simply have to, even
if friends have to remain friends forever,
and the people you love have to
remain people you love forever,
and if your reaction towards enemies could always be hate
and never love,
then nothing can change.
Then just stop. That was simple,
even with Buddhism, then it couldn't change, because
I couldn't change it either, so
today things always stay the same.
But if you couldn't change,
then it doesn't exist, not even
from us. If
you couldn't change, then
it couldn't exist, even
if it could come from me, then it couldn't
change. If I couldn't change
my reaction,
if I couldn't change my friends,
then even causing and acting would
n't exist. Cool, or
even fans from here would come if
I didn't change.  could and one
has not how my view over could change
then these things could not
change then I could
not turn my things around even
if they came from me
even the seeds that would come from me would
then not be beneficial under
which always in the dead end and the
devil would control my mind
and I don't know what
I would probably go somewhere else
[Music]
where are you yes
casually
get the announcement behind me because
sometimes sometimes forgotten then
I feel bad afterwards
that I didn't forget we have two
announcements for you
okay here goes
this is a very special project so
mountain
and I am very sad that we say
yes it was cool will be so strong in Arizona
we have decided that
nobody is coming this spring but
next fall next fall
we will invite you after the end for
a retweet
but
last just advertising for me
and we did a fundraising because we
want trees neither in the north 20
150 years before when the cowboys cut down the
trees in the mid mountain
we did a
fundraising in November
we  We tried to raise one hundred thousand dollars.
We wanted to plant 3,000 trees with it,
and we succeeded! On the last
night of Wild Wings, we
raised one hundred thousand dollars,
and that was the easy part.
Now someone has to dig the holes, and we
want to put that money back in.
You still can't come tomorrow.
All year round, you can
visit us. You can retweet
old people. The thunder will come
there in April to make a difference,
and we'll have a one-month budget
there, and you are very much invited to
this rather short system.
[Music]
You are very welcome to come and
help us plant the trees, or
you can donate even more money for the
trees.
These are all the new books
ahead, and since then, in Qatar Press, all of a sudden,
we have a lot
here. There's one in the commentary on carrying the stove, there's one
in the commentary on
carrying the diamond cutter, and a
new book, Majority Meditation.
[Music]
A new book, whether we
are just the mind school of the doctor,
and there's a new translation of the
medical ultras. That's five new
books that have come out here.  are
and that's the hard work, the mix
makes it, working very hard the next night, as
I said yesterday,
they are working on 27 books at the moment and
I must say
that we see the results of the
book
and we had sponsors from Austria
and Germany who
helped us pay the translators
and I want to thank them and
I want to congratulate you and without the
RLL project we could
n't make these books anyway, since Gold
Clubs
in the Russian-speaking world
and other Gold Clubs
work in various places in the DACH region,
you really help us a lot, only through
your help
can we translate them,
I don't think any of these books have ever been
translated before, it's very
exciting and they are very, very deep,
all of Master Kam L'Aquila's
meditation instructions are in
Mountain Blood Ballast,
the teacher's book as meditation, that the whole
translation of the meditation course is
there in the book of the Golden
Key, the red book in the middle is
the best book about the new school that has ever been
translated and it's
incredible and that's what Schneider means
Sutter's commentary and the heart and
regiments
are so beautiful when you can have them at
home. I like to read them at breakfast.
I put my computer
on the breakfast table and slowly eat
breakfast and I just read a few
lines from Sutter's work.
You can order all of them as your book via
email.
You can scan the QR code and in a few
minutes it will be with you. The hard
work of Gustav. Click on it and he ran
at the bar and
all these people work so hard and you
can get the books and the best thing about it
is
[Music]
that with language publishers, like
in Germany,
they are very experienced and their hard
work
with Edition Blu Blumenau, the
publisher in Hamburg or wherever they are
now. I'm going to see if she lived in the Black
Forest.
She publishes the books,
not more books than anyone else in the
world, and if you are there yourself, then
you say they made a short young man and they
will post in German and Russian.
Then you have questions
[Music]
yes, of course,
one of the questions that came in
from
When I've heard about all these different people, all these teams,
I start to hurt myself for
all the bad things I've done,
and I feel
so guilty.
How can I think about it? Is there
a way I
can plant seeds so that I don't
feel guilty and don't blame myself? It
's a great question, a
really, really good question, and
I'd like to tell you the solutions to this problem.
When he
gets the book about the heating meditation, there's
a chapter called
Low Self-Esteem. And
if you really understand the first Panchen Lama,
then
theoretically you should
have super low self-esteem.
And why? Because you suddenly understand
that everything in this world comes from you,
and you think, oh my god. And you think,
as described, I already felt
bad before. I thought
it was just my husband, now
suddenly it's everyone,
and here in America, our last one, the
president. I know I'm not supposed to talk about
politics, but it was immediately
depressing to
think that we could do that.
[Music]
And there's a discussion about it
in  If he reads the book
specifically about this question, what if I
truly understand
that all this stuff, all these
bad things in the world, are already
coming to me? Then I'll be overwhelmed
by the fact of how bad I must be.
And then there's this special
meditation technique, it costs over
$400. Tell me, what does it necessarily
mean? Doesn't
any of you want to make money? Wait a minute,
I wanted my best marksman,
that was too easy. I'm not giving out any money
for just our ten tipsters.
I'll give you a hint.
I know that increase is... I know
when you start to feel
slowly tired in
meditation.
What do you do when
I'm from 11?
I'll give you my tipsters. It
means
it's okay. It's true,
every stupid person,
including many Americans, comes
from you. It's a mistake, that's true,
but
everything more beautiful in this world
also comes from you. Logically speaking, every
intelligent person,
every kind person, every
charity, every mother who gives her
life for her children,
every kind of service to the world counts,
everything comes from you as well.
And yes, that's true.
Yes, you
also have all these crazy people
who want war or to
achieve power.  You also created these people,
but I would say there are
many more good people in the
world that you have created just as much. You
have all these wonderful
billions of people
who quietly do
good things all day long.
Parents
who give up the first 20 years of their lives for
their child. Here in America, when
a child graduates from college,
the parents go to Europe for vacation. You know,
the whole world is full of
parents. Isn't it true,
Markus, that the first 20 years are given
for the child, and you have
created all these people? And I
think it's true,
it's correct that there are more good
people in the world than bad ones. It's
only because the good people
aren't as loud as the bad ones that the good ones aren't.
But there are billions of people
who
give something every day for their children, for their
parents. You don't hear anything about it
in the news.
They are
hardly mentioned online either, but there are billions of
them, and you have created them all.
So,
super
smooth, just a pat on the back.
Good job, you have created all these parents of the
world.  Monkeys, that's pretty
cool.
Okay, then we'll take a break.
Yeah, just one more question.
While we're listening to all this, including this
debate between the devil and the
angel in our minds, the question is, how
can I plant seeds so that I
listen more to the angel than the devil?
I have a hole. I have a
suggestion that immediately comes to mind, and
I understand the question. All day
long,
and there we are all the same: the best
person here
in the Sahara and the worst, the
worst person here in this world.
If you're in this world, these
two only differ by one
percent. Okay, if you're here, you've already...
[Music]
I've always been something, so the
nicest person and also the worst
person in this world are pretty
similar. There are hardly any differences,
maybe one percent or so. If you're
stuck in this world
involuntarily, if you're not an emulation,
then yeah, then you hear the devil
talking in your head all day,
and then you even say to yourself, "Ca
n't I just get a break?"
Even in the book, the angel only speaks
sometimes, but when you're in my head,
I hardly ever hear the angel. It's
only the devil. And how do I get more
of the angel in my mind?
You all know that I got
married not too long ago,
and
my wife told me you're a
great speaker
and
I enjoy coming to the college and listening to
the lectures. You talk all day long,
somewhere, but
then to hear that it's somehow
not that well developed.
You can speak much better, but
your ears need more practice.
You don't really listen well. And
I have this feeling that
the angel speaks in our minds,
but we don't hear it. And I think that
's a difference.
I think maybe there's some kind of
rule in the universe that the angel is allowed to
speak 50 percent of the time and the devil is allowed to speak 50 percent of
the time.
But we have a problem with
listening; we don't hear the angel. Why does
she speak to us?
But we try  Not listening, and
I think that's something we could practice,
especially in your meditation. There's
a special meditation
you can do for this called
silent listening. In your meditation,
you can try it for fun,
and he just listens silently. You sit down, you assume
your eight-point posture,
the eight-point posture,
and instead of imagining an object
in your mind, just listen. Try to listen
more to the angel.
Open your ears,
and listening becomes your object.
I think that's a kind of fixation
meditation.
Try it; sometimes it really is fun.
Instead of
choosing an external object,
just sit for 15
minutes
and listen to
[music].
And you can, of course, also listen to things like the garbage truck
and other such
things.
Later, he'll also hear your heartbeat,
and
even later, you can even
hear the oxygen
beating against Europe. Just go
deeper and deeper, deeper and deeper, just listen,
and
quiet messages will come from your angel. It
will reach your ear.  Whisper, and
you have to be patient.
This doesn't just happen after a day
or two. You have to try it for a week or two.
Just sit in meditation and
listen.
At first, you'll hear all the noise:
children, millers, dogs
barking. Then go deeper
and deeper.
Go to a place of silence and
just listen and open yourself up.
I would say you will
begin to hear the angel. You will be
able to hear beautiful things.
It's a truly wonderful
practice
and requires more coffee.